{
  "id": "lifeandstyle/2020/nov/28/what-links-oliver-and-moulin-rouge-the-weekend-quiz",
  "date": "2020-11-28T07:00:02Z",
  "title": "What links Oliver and Moulin Rouge? The Weekend quiz",
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "Who rallied the troops at Tilbury?",
      "questionHtml": "Who rallied the troops at Tilbury?",
      "answer": "Elizabeth I (1588)",
      "answerHtml": "Elizabeth I (1588)"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "What school of psychology is named after the German for “form”?",
      "questionHtml": "What school of psychology is named after the German for “form”?",
      "answer": "Gestalt",
      "answerHtml": "Gestalt"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "Florence Thompson was the subject of which Dorothea Lange photograph?",
      "questionHtml": "Florence Thompson was the subject of which Dorothea Lange photograph?",
      "answer": "Migrant Mother",
      "answerHtml": "Migrant Mother"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "What rose from £30 to £45 in April?",
      "questionHtml": "What rose from £30 to £45 in April?",
      "answer": "Contactless payment limit",
      "answerHtml": "Contactless payment limit"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "Which six EU members are monarchies?",
      "questionHtml": "Which six EU members are monarchies?",
      "answer": "Belgium, Denmark, Luxembourg, Netherlands, Spain and Sweden",
      "answerHtml": "Belgium, Denmark, Luxembourg, Netherlands, Spain and Sweden"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "What was built in Paris to house the Crown of Thorns?",
      "questionHtml": "What was built in Paris to house the Crown of Thorns?",
      "answer": "Sainte-Chapelle",
      "answerHtml": "Sainte-Chapelle"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "Part of the space weather forecast, what is a CME?",
      "questionHtml": "Part of the space weather forecast, what is a CME?",
      "answer": "Coronal mass ejection (from the sun)",
      "answerHtml": "Coronal mass ejection (from the sun)"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "type": "NORMAL",
      "question": "Which Labour leader climbed 108 Munros",
      "questionHtml": "Which Labour leader climbed 108 Munros",
      "answer": "John Smith",
      "answerHtml": "John Smith"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Dorothy L Sayers; Fay Weldon; Don DeLillo; Salman Rushdie?",
      "questionHtml": "Dorothy L Sayers; Fay Weldon; Don DeLillo; Salman Rushdie?",
      "answer": "Novelists who worked as advertising copywriters",
      "answerHtml": "Novelists who worked as advertising copywriters"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Archibald Ormsby-Gore; Alan Measles; Pudsey?",
      "questionHtml": "Archibald Ormsby-Gore; Alan Measles; Pudsey?",
      "answer": "Teddy bears: John Betjeman’s; Grayson Perry’s; Children in Need mascot",
      "answerHtml": "Teddy bears: John Betjeman’s; Grayson Perry’s; Children in Need mascot"
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Shields; America; Carolina; Korea?",
      "questionHtml": "Shields; America; Carolina; Korea?",
      "answer": "Places with North and South prefixes",
      "answerHtml": "Places with North and South prefixes"
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Clydesdale; Suffolk; Shire; Percheron?",
      "questionHtml": "Clydesdale; Suffolk; Shire; Percheron?",
      "answer": "Draught horse breeds",
      "answerHtml": "Draught horse breeds"
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Concrete; Palatinate; Varsity; Cherwell?",
      "questionHtml": "Concrete; Palatinate; Varsity; Cherwell?",
      "answer": "Student newspapers: UEA; Durham; Cambridge; Oxford",
      "answerHtml": "Student newspapers: UEA; Durham; Cambridge; Oxford"
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Oklahoma; Hello, Dolly; Oliver; Twang; Moulin Rouge?",
      "questionHtml": "Oklahoma; Hello, Dolly; Oliver; Twang; Moulin Rouge?",
      "answer": "Musicals and film musicals missing exclamation marks",
      "answerHtml": "Musicals and film musicals missing exclamation marks"
    },
    {
      "number": 15,
      "type": "WHAT_LINKS",
      "question": "Al Oerter; Carl Lewis; Michael Phelps; Kaori Icho?",
      "questionHtml": "Al Oerter; Carl Lewis; Michael Phelps; Kaori Icho?",
      "answer": "Won four consecutive Olympic golds in the same event: discus; long jump; 200m medley swimming; women’s 63kg wrestling",
      "answerHtml": "Won four consecutive Olympic golds in the same event: discus; long jump; 200m medley swimming; women’s 63kg wrestling"
    }
  ]
}
